Register of the World War I subject collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Picture booklet, "Ruines de Liége Pendant La Guerre de 1914," (Box-folder 32: 43)
- Postcards/Postkarten, undated (Box-folder 32: 44)
  In French, German, and English.
- Postcards showing the destruction caused by the war, undated (Box-folder 32: 45)
- Poster, "Hello Doughboys!...,", undated (Box-folder 32: 46)
- Poster, "Kill that Eagle,", 1914 (Box-folder 32: 47)
- Poster, "Reden ist silber…,", undated (Box-folder 32: 48)
- Poster, "Vorläufiger Ausweis…,", 1918 (Box-folder 32: 49)
- Window posters showing support for U.S. war effort, undated (Box-folder 32: 50)
- Materials re Kriegsanleihe [war bonds], circa 1917 (Box-folder 32: 51)
- Russian government war bonds, 1916 (Box-folder 32: 52)
- Russian Railway Service in Siberia and Japan, 1918 [CDs], 2002 (Box-folder 32: 53)
  One CD is titled "Russian Railway Service in Siberia," and consists of photos by 2nd Lt. William C. Jones of the Russian Railway Service, ©2002. The other CD is titled "Russian Railway Service 1918 - Japan," ©2002 by Dale C. Jones, fair use allowed, please credit 2nd Lt. William C. Jones.
- The St.-Nazaire Memorial, 1925, undated (Box-folder 32: 54)
- British ration books, undated (Box-folder 33: 1)
- German food cards and orders, undated (Box-folder 33: 2)
- German ration cards, undated (Box-folder 33: 3)
- Russian sugar ration cards, 1916 (Box-folder 33: 4)
- Newton D. Baker materials, 1917-1919, 1949 (Box-folder 33: 5)
  Newton D. Baker was the U.S. Secretary of War during World War I. Included are: typescript copies of excerpts from Baker's papers at the Library of Congress; and a typescript biography of Baker, written by James H. Durbin in 1949 (wartime assistant to Mr. Baker).
- Divisions und Korpstagesbefehle, 1918 (Box-folder 33: 6-7)
- Goldbuch für Wehrmann Fritz Franz Podsun, circa 1917-1918 (Box-folder 33: 8)
- Claude Houser materials, circa 1918-1919 (Box-folder 33: 9)
  These materials were evidently collected by Houser and have been kept together. Includes: a leave slip; American Expeditionary Forces General Orders No. 38-A (a statement of thanks from Commander-in-Chief Pershing); correspondence; "My Soldier's Record" booklet; newspaper clippings; Grenade Training Manual; and vouchers (French and German) to be redeemed after the war.
- Tagebuch, circa 1914 (Box-folder 33: 10)
  Handwritten diary of a German soldier. A note with the book says that the writer died in France on 30 October 1914 near Lille.
- France, miscellaneous, circa 1919 (Box-folder 33: 11)
  Consists of an index, "Documents sur la Guerre."
- Germany, miscellaneous, 1912-1918 (Box-folder 33: 12)
  Includes a newspaper clipping; materials related to the publication of particular books (order form, advertisement); a flyer; and correspondence regarding a German soldier, Georg Rosenberg.
- Italy, miscellaneous, 1918 (Box-folder 33: 13)
  Includes flyers, leaflets, a newsletter, a typescript, and programs. In Italian.
- United States, miscellaneous, 1918, 1968, undated (Box-folder 33: 14)
  Includes an excerpt of a typescript about production of food products with a summary of nutritive values, as well as two pieces of correspondence: a letter from the United States Ambassador in France to a Professor Graham Lusk regarding an Inter-Allied Commission on Alimentation meeting; and a 1968 letter enclosing material relating to the American Ouvroir Funds (the material, in French, is included).
- Books, 1909-1910, 1914-1919 (Box 34)
  - Standarten wehn und Fahnen, undated
  - Das neue Gartenbuch, circa 1916
  - Französisch für Offiziere und Mannschaften, 1916
  - Die heilige Wehr, 1917
  - Ein Günstling des Kaisers, 1919
  - Der deutsche Kriegskalander, 1915
  - Kriegsbrot für die Seele, 1917
  - Totendank, 1918
  - Was Hunnen und Barbaren Singen, 1915
  - Das Kommandobuch, 1916
  - Die Ausbildung Infanteristen, 1915
  - Vor Ypern, 1916
  - Himmelsblumen auf Heldengräber, 1916
  - Gebetbuch mit Sterbebilderalbum, 1909
  - Mein Krieg, 1918
  - Litauischer Sprachführer, undated
  - Stolz ziehn wir in die Schlacht, circa 1918
  - Waffen des Wortes, 1914-1915
  - Der katholische Soldat, 1910
- Oversize Materials, 1894, 1911-1926, 1933 (Boxes 35-42, map case)
  See also: Boxes 13-16.
  - Book, Peace Edition of the Worcester Telegram Commemorating Worcester's Part in the World War, 1919 July 31 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - Drawing, "Den Preussiske Slughals,", circa 1915 (Box-folder 35: 2)
  - Drawing, "Satirieke Kaart van Europa,", circa 1915
    "Het Gekkenhuis (Oud Liedje, Nieuwe Wijs)." By Louis Raemaekers.
  - Drawing, Sperr und Vernichtungsfeuer, Artl. Kdr. 227, 1918 July
  - List, "Passenger List of Organizations and Casuals Returning to the United States,", undated
    For Company "E," 107th Engineers.
  - Map, Artillerie-Aufstellung im Abschnill 'G,', 1918 September (Box-folder 35: 3)
  - Map, Bétheniville, Planmaterial der 3. Armee, 1918
  - Map, [Cantigny, France], rolling barrage and its immediate protection, 1918 May
  - Map, Crouy-sur-Ourcq, circa 1918 August 17
  - Map, Crouy-sur-Ourcq, circa 1918 August 31
  - Map, Meuse-Argonne Offensive, 1919 May 24 (Box-folder 35: 4)
    "Map showing Daily Position of Front Line, as well as the Area of Operations, the Successive Advances by Date, and the Relative Position and Designation of the Divisions in Line of the American Army During the Meuse-Argonne Offensive."
  - Map, The New Europe, 1919 June
    Map of post-war Europe, with text along the top stating that "There are no Boundaries to the Future of the Man who Saves" and along the edges stating that "War Savings Stamps Pay Dividends To The Thrifty."
  - Map, [Northern France], undated
    Portion of a larger map with handwritten/drawn annotations in red/orange and green, some of which seem to indicate the positions of military officials. The map itself is a 1912 revision.
  - Map, Noviant, 1918 April
  - Map, Order of Battle on the Western Front at 11 A.M., November 11, 1918, circa 1918 November
    "This sheet covers both the Allied and German Forces; the position of the headquarters of their Commanders-in-Chief; the commanders and headquarters of the Army Groups and Armies, the location of the different Divisions involved, both in line, in support, and in reserve, as well as the service of supply; and generally, the tabulated strength and condition of both forces."
  - Map, Ravensteins Kriegskarte der Umgegend von Paris (Kriegskarte Nr. 5), undated (Box-folder 35: 5)
  - Map, Sketch of Traverse from Montfaucon to Cunel via Cierges, Gesnes and Romagne, undated
  - Map, Sketch of Traverse from Montfaucon to Cunel via Nantillois, undated
  - Map, Sketch of Traverse from Montfaucon to Dannevoux via Septsarges, undated
  - Map, Zone of Action, Location of Combat Units, Posts of Command, Boche Divisions Opposite, and Objectives, of the "Wildcat," 81st Division, in Meuse-Argonne Offensive, circa 1918 November
  - Newspaper, The A.E.F. University News, 1919 May 22 (Box-folder 35: 6)
  - Newspaper, The Morning Union [special edition], "War Ends,", 1918 November 11
  - Poster, American flag, undated
  - Poster, "Aufruf zur Gestellung. Seine Majestät der Kaiser haben die Mobilmachung der Armee und der Marine befohlen,", circa 1914 August
  - Poster, "Bekanntmachung. Allen Einwohnern Ostpreussens,", 1914 August
  - Poster, "Caring for American Soldiers in England,", circa 1918 (Box-folder 35: 7)
    Bulletin No. 7 issued by the War Council of the American Red Cross.
  - Poster, "Co-operation Between Public and Railroads Inspires Nation-wide Comment by Editors,", circa 1917 September
  - Poster, "Denkt an das Rote Kreuz!,", circa August 1915
  - Poster, "Editorial Comment on the Way Railroads Are Doing Their Bit to Help Win the War,", circa 1917 August
  - Poster, French flag, undated
  - Poster, "Hier wird Kriegsanleihe gezeichnet!,", circa 1918 March (Box-folder 35: 8)
  - Poster, "Loading Plan of Caisson, Company Tool Wagon,", 1917 October 16
    Features diagram of layout, plus detailed lists of supplies, with their amounts and locations.
  - Poster, "The Red Cross Supplies 30,000 People Each Week With Information Concerning Relatives in the Fighting Forces at Home and Overseas,", circa 1918
    Bulletin No. 10 issued by the War Council of the American Red Cross.
  - Press release, "Special Editorial Series--No. 4,", 1918 June
    From the National War Savings Committee, three articles ("Thrift With a Purpose," "What War Saving Does," and "The Preparedness of Thrift") on War Savings for use in daily newspapers.
  - Newspaper, La Libre Belgique, No. 172, 1918 November 18 (Box 36)
    Consists of a photocopy of the issue.
  - Newspaper clippings, Franz Ferdinand (Archduke of Austria), circa 1926
    German newspaper clippings (originals and photocopies) from 1924-1926 about Archduke Franz Ferdinand and a plan for reorganizing the Austro-Hungarian monarchy.
  - Booklet, G2, 4th Army Corps, 1918-1919
    Includes a roster of personnel in the Second Section, G.S., Fourth Army Corps, American Expeditionary Forces, as well as essays/stories, cartoons, and poems.
  - Cartoons, "Bunte Kriegsbilderbogen," Verlag Vereinigung der Kunstfreunde, Nos. 1-14, undated
  - Cartoons, "Kriegszeit Künstler Flugblätter," No. 1 - No.64/65, 1914-1916
  - Book, The A.E.F. in Cartoon - by Wally, 1933 (Box 37)
  - Book, Uniformen Der alten Armee, undated
    Published by the Waldorf Astoria Zigarettenfabrik GmbH, München. Contains 312 color printed cigarette cards of various German Army uniforms.
  - Booklets, Saskatoon Board of Trade, Letter File, 1917
    Three booklets: January-February, March-April, and May-December.
  - Scrapbooks, circa 1914-1919 (Boxes 37-39)
    - Newspaper and magazine clippings, 1919 January (Box 37)
      Covers the United States and its involvement in the war. Also includes some ephemera.
    - Cartoons saved during the "World War," 1914-1918, post-1918 (Box 38)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1914-1918 (Box 39)
      Compiled by Mary L. Schofield, January 29, 1916.
    - World War I clipping collection, 1914
  - Sheet music, 1912-1918 (Box 40)
    - American, 1914-1918 (Box-folder 40: 1-12)
      - "Belgium Dry Your Tears,", 1918 (Box-folder 40: 1)
      - "Bring Back My Daddy to Me,", 1917
      - "Bye-Bye, My Sailor Boy, Jack-Tar,", 1916
      - "The Dream of a Soldier Boy,", 1917 (Box-folder 40: 2)
      - "Good-Bye Broadway, Hello France,", 1917
      - "Good-Bye, Good Luck, God Bless You,", 1916
      - "Hello Central! Give Me No Man's Land,", 1918 (Box-folder 40: 3)
      - "I Want to Go Back to 'Blighty,'", 1918
      - "If You Don't Like Our President Wilson (You Knife the Land that Feeds Us All),", 1917
      - "I'm a Long Way from Tipperary,", 1914 (Box-folder 40: 4)
      - "I'm All Dressed Up to Kill,", 1918
      - "I'm Goin' to Fight My Way Right Back to Carolina,", 1918
      - "I'm Going to Follow the Boys,", 1917 (Box-folder 40: 5)
      - "In Time of Peace Prepare for War,", 1915
      - "Just a Baby's Prayer at Twilight (for Her Daddy Over There),", 1918
      - "Let's All Be Americans Now,", 1917 (Box-folder 40: 6)
      - "Let Us Boys Fight for Our Nation (and Stick to the U.S.A.),", 1917
      - "Liberty Bell (It's Time to Ring Again),", 1917
      - "The Little Grey Mother Who Waits All Alone,", 1915 (Box-folder 40: 7)
      - "Lorraine (My Beautiful Alsace Lorraine),", 1917
      - "My Yankee Boy,", 1917
      - "Oh! Frenchy,", 1918 (Box-folder 40: 8)
      - "Sing for Liberty and Keep Them Singing,", circa 1918
        Mostly lyrics, though some music and lyrics, to a variety of patriotic songs: "For Your Boy and My Boy," "For the Boys Over There," "K-K-K-Katy," "Uncle Sam He's Got the Infantry," "Smiles," "Battle Hymn of the Republic," "Onward, Christian Soldiers," "Keep the Home Fires Burning," "There's a Long, Long Trail," "Over There," "The Marseillaise," "We'll Be Waiting When You Come Back Home," "The Star-Spangled Banner," "My Country, 'Tis of Thee."
      - "So Long, Mother,", 1917
      - "A Soldier's Rosary,", 1918 (Box-folder 40: 9)
      - "Somewhere in France Is the Lily,", 1917
      - "There's a Service Flag Flying at Our House,", 1917
      - "We'll Be Ready Whenever You Call,", 1916 (Box-folder 40: 10)
      - "What Are You Going to Do to Help the Boys?,", 1918
      - "When Alexander Takes His Ragtime Band to France,", 1918
      - "When I Come Back to You (We'll Have a Yankee-Doodle Wedding),", 1918 (Box-folder 40: 11)
      - "When Yankee Doodle Goes to France,", 1917
      - "When Yankee Doodle Learns to 'Parlez Vous Français,'", 1917
      - "When Yankee Doodle Met His Dixie Down in Delaware,", 1910 (Box-folder 40: 12)
      - "When You Come Back My Soldier Boy,", 1918
      - "Your Lips Are No Man's Land But Mine,", 1918
    - French, 1915-1917 (Box-folder 40: 13-17)
      - "L'An Prochain,", 1915 (Box-folder 40: 13)
      - "Après la Victoire,", 1915
        Paroles et musique de René Fauchois.
      - "Après la Victoire,", 1916
        Paroles de André Rosa, musique de Héloïse Rouyer.
      - "Aux Héros!,", 1915 (Box-folder 40: 14)
      - "Le Calvaire Brisé,", circa 1915
      - "Délivrance!,", 1916
      - "Des Croix sur les Chemins,", circa 1916 (Box-folder 40: 15)
      - "Les Enfants de France,", 1917
      - "Hymnes et Chants Nationaux des Alliés,", undated
        Booklet includes music and lyrics to 12 songs: "La Marseillaise (Chant National)," "Le chant du départ (Hymne Guerrier)," "La Brabançonne (Chant National Belge)," "God save the King (Hymne National Anglais)," "Hymne national Russe," "Hymne national Serbe," "Hymne National Italien," "Hymne national de la Grèce," "Hymne national du Japon," "Hymne national Roumain," "Hymne de Mameli (Chant National Italien)," "Hymne national du Monténégro." In French and the respective languages of the national anthems.
      - "Maman!,", 1916 (Box-folder 40: 16)
      - "La Marche des Poilus,", 1915
      - "Petits Poëmes de Guerre (1914-1916),", circa 1916
        This is the title of a series of individually published songs. This copy is of the song "La Bouffarde."
      - "Le Rêve,", undated (Box-folder 40: 17)
      - "Sous la Neige Blanche,", circa 1915
      - "L'Union Latine,", undated
      - "Les Vieux Poilus,", circa 1915
    - Polish, 1912 (Box-folder 40: 18)
      - "Kwiecisty I Wonny Maj"
  - Booklet, "The Song of the Seventy-Five,", 1919 (Box-folder 41: 1)
    By Grantland Rice, 2nd Lieutenant, 115th Artillery, A.E.F.
  - Booklet, "Über Land und Meer,", 1915
  - Calendar, "We Shall Not Sleep,", 1919 (Box-folder 41: 2)
    Published as a supplement to the Springfield News-Record, 8 February 1919, this calendar was "distributed by arrangement with Bauer & Black, Makers of Surgical Dressings, etc., Chicago, New York, Toronto" on behalf of the soldiers and as a memorial to those who died. It includes an illustration by Philip Lyford and the poem "We Shall Not Sleep" by Lieutenant Colonel Dr. John McCrae.
  - Certificate, authorized agent of the Treasury Department, circa 1918
    Issued to Thomas M. Rafter, Agent, Wells Fargo & Company, Nevada, California. It authorizes him to "receive and issue at the cost prices indicated thereon United States War-Savings Certificate Stamps and United States Thrift Stamps."
  - Drawing, "La Lettera al fronte," Credito Italiano, 1917
  - Drawing, portrait of man in military attire on a horse, circa 1916 (Box-folder 41: 3)
    By Richard B. Adam.
  - Etchings, scenes from France and Belgium, circa 1918-1919
    Typed captions accompanying the etchings attribute them to E. Kufferath, but the signature on the etchings themselves appears to read C. Kufferath. Many of the etchings relate to the United States 91st Division and its activities.
  - Flyer, "Hunger!,", undated
  - Flyer, "Milchkarten,", 1916 September (Box-folder 41: 4)
  - Flyer, "Milchkarten,", 1916 October
  - Flyer, "Schweigen verkürzt…,", undated
  - Leaflet, "Briefe aus Deutschland,", 1916
    Blätter zum Studium der Wirtschaftlichen lage in den Kriegführenden Ländern.
  - Leaflet, "Een maand van overwinningen aan het Britsche front,", 1917 April
    In Dutch, French, Swedish, and Danish.
  - Leaflet, "Engineer Operations Bulletin,", 1918 November 15 (Box-folder 41: 5)
    Published by the Office of Chief Engineer, American E.F., Technical Information Section. Features an article titled "Engineer replacement regiment trains thousands of recruits each month."
  - Leaflets, "Leipziger Neueste Nachrichten,", 1916
  - Leaflet, "Der Völkerfriede,", 1918 January 17
  - Leaflet, "Walk. Ein baltisches Stadtbild,", undated
    In German, Estonian and Latvian.
  - Leaflet, "Wisoms Laukininku Moteroms musu Tewisskes,", undated
  - Leaflet, "Zeichnet die Kriegsanleihe. Deutschland die Insel des Friedens,", undated
  - Map, Etain and Montfaucon, 79th Division, circa 1918 November (Box-folder 41: 6)
    "Reduction of Etain and Montfaucon Maps, showing the 79th Division's Sector and the positions of its front line, day by day, during the Last Phase of the Meuse-Argonne Battle."
  - Map, Front de Verdun, circa 1916 December
  - Map, Montdidier 21C, Karte von Frankreich, Gruppe 1, undated
  - Map, Montdidier 21D, Karte von Frankreich, Gruppe 1, undated
  - Map, Montfaucon, 79th Division, circa 1918 September
    "Reduction of Montfaucon Sheet, showing the 79th Division's Sector and the positions of its front line, day by day, during the First Phase of the Meuse-Argonne Battle."
  - Map, Operation West of the Meuse, Oct. 1st-12th, 1st Div. A.E.F., circa 1918 October (Box-folder 41: 7)
  - Map, St. Mihiel Operation, 1st Div. A.E.F., Sept. 12-13, circa 1918 September
  - Map, Souilly and St. Mihiel, 79th Division, circa 1918 October
    "Reduction of Souilly and St. Mihiel Maps, showing the 79th Division's Sector and the positions of its front line, during its occupation of the Troyon Sector."
  - Map, Tracing for St. Mihiel, 1918
  - Map, Traverse 22 (continued), from Station 35 of Traverse 22 to Consenvoye, undated
  - Map, Traverse No. 1, from Essey to Flirey, 1918 (Box-folder 41: 8)
  - Map, U.S. Army Map, [Flanders, Belgium], undated
  - Map, U.S. Army Map, [Northeastern France], undated
  - Map, Verdun 35C, Karte von Frankreich, Gruppe I, undated
  - Newspaper, Berliner Lokal-Anzeiger [special edition], 1914
    Two issues: 31 July 1914, featuring an article titled "Russland will den Krieg!" and 1 August 1914, featuring an article titled "Allgemeine Mobilmachung in Deutschland."
  - Newspaper, Lloyd Ottoman, "L'Entente et Brest-Litowsk,", 1917 December 31 (Box-folder 41: 9)
    French translation of "L'Osmanischer Lloyd." Only the top half of the newspaper pages are present; the bottom half seems to have been torn off.
  - Newspaper, Nieuwe Rotterdamsche Courant, "Hoe de oorlog ontstond,", 1919 November 29
    By Karl Kautsky.
  - Newspaper, O Seculo Comico, 1914-1916
    In Portuguese.
  - Newspaper, Qu'est-ce Que C'est?, 1919 (Box-folder 41: 10)
    Published by the American students of the University of Toulouse. Two issues: Vol. 1, No. 3, 2 April 1919, and Vol. 1, No. 10, 21 May 1919. In English and French.
  - Poster, "An die Bevölkerung des XI. Korpsbezirks,", 1914 August 1
  - Poster, "Aufruf. Sammelt ausländisches Geld!,", undated
    Preussischer Landesverein vom Roten Kreuz.
  - Poster, "Bekanntmachung. Auf Befehl Seiner Majestät des Kaisers und Königs ist für das Reichsgebiet der Kriegszustand erklärt…,", 1914 August 1
  - Poster, "Important Notice! President of the United States Proclaims Friday June 28, 1918 as National War Savings Day,", circa 1918 June
    Produced by the United States Government War Savings Committee for California (North), urging the people of California to sign pledges for subscriptions for War Savings Stamps.
  - Poster, "Naczelny Komitet Narodowy,", circa 1915 (Box-folder 41: 11)
  - Poster, "Universal Membership Week, Red Cross Christmas Roll Call, Dec. 16-23rd,", circa 1918 December
    Two copies of the poster, though both are torn and missing the first half.
  - Press release, "War's Cost and Length Depends Upon Civilians,", circa 1918 June
    From the National War Savings Committee, written by George M. Reynolds, President of the Continental and Commercial National Bank of Chicago.
  - Printed matter, "La Vie Parisienne,", 1918 August 3
  - Timetable, Kommandeur der Kraftfahrtruppen Nr. 2, Stafetten-Fahrplan, 1918 January 16
  - Correspondence, Telegrammy, 1914 July 22 (Box-folder 42: 1)
    In Russian.
  - Map, Ailly-sur-Noye, Karte der 2. Armee, 1918 July
  - Map, Amiens - Map Showing Divisions Re-Entering Line, 1918
    "Each division is shown at point where last identified before being withdrawn and where identified when it returned to line."
  - Map, Amiens, undated
    Dressé, gravé et publié par le Service géographique de l'armée
  - Map, Artillerie Zielfelder Karte, Bodenständig gehört zur Stellung, circa 1917 December
    Abgeschlossen am 21.12.17.
  - Map, Carte du Front Français, undated (Box-folder 42: 2)
  - Map, Châlons (Carte de France et des Frontières, No. 17), undated
  - Map, Bernécourt, circa 1918 July
    Abgeschlossen 18.7.18.
  - Map, Environs de Bar-le-Duc, 1913
  - Map, German Defensive Organizations, Vicinity of Montfaucon, 1919 March
    Surveyed by G-2-C 1st Army, November and December 1918. Two versions - they have the same title but are slightly different from each other.
  - Map, Gironville, circa 1918 February (Box-folder 42: 3)
    Abgeschlossen am 4.2.18.
  - Map, Gironville, circa 1918 May
    Abgeschlossen am 21.5.18.
  - Map, Gironville, circa 1918 June
    Abgeschlossen am 18.6.18.
  - Map, Marvoison, circa 1917 August
    Abgeschlossen am 27.8.17.
  - Map, Metz (Carte de France et des Frontières, No. 18), undated
  - Map, Metz S.O., Road and Bridge Map, undated (Box-folder 42: 4)
  - Map, [Nonsard, France], circa 1918
  - Map, [Northern France], Stoverm 7, 1918 June
  - Map, Objectives for Interdiction Fire, A.I.S. 1st Army, [Northern France], 1918 September
  - Map, Organized German Position, Vicinity of Montfaucon, 1919 March (Box-folder 42: 5)
    Surveyed by G-2-C 1st Army, November and December 1918.
  - Map, Pont-a-Mousson, 1918 April
  - Map, Richecourt, circa 1917 August
    Abgeschlossen am 30.8.17.
  - Map, Richecourt, circa 1917 December
    Abgeschlossen am 5.12.17.
  - Map, St. Baussant, circa 1917 August
    Abgeschlossen am 28.8.17
  - Map, St. Mihiel - Pont a Mousson Sector, 1918 October (Box-folder 42: 6)
  - Map, St. Mihiel Sector, 1918 December
  - Map, Sarrebourg, 1911
  - Map, Seicheprey, circa 1918 March
    Abgeschlossen am 19.3.18.
  - Map, Thiaucourt, circa 1918 May
    Abgeschlossen am 26.5.18.
  - Map, Thiaucourt S-W, circa 1918 May (Box-folder 42: 7)
    Abgeschlossen am 27.5.18.
  - Map, Thiaucourt N.O., circa 1918 June
    Abgeschlossen am 11.6.18.
  - Map, Thiaucourt, circa 1918 July
    Abgeschlossen am 30.7.18.
  - Map, Unterstände in der Pariser-Stellung, undated
  - Map, Verdun (Mézières), 1913
  - Map, Verdun, 1918 September (Box-folder 42: 8)
  - Map, Verkehr beim Feinde, Februar Ausgabe, 1918 February
    Nach Truppen-, Fliegermeldungen Gefangenen-Aussagen, Angab des Artl. Messtrupps u.s.w. zusammengestellt von Kartenstelle 7. d. Verm. Abt. 2.
  - Map, Verkehr beim Feinde, März Ausgabe, 1918 March
  - Map, Xivray, circa 1918 March
    Abgeschlossen am 1.3.18.
  - Map, Zusammenstellung der Erkundungs-Ergebnisse [Northern France], circa 1918 July
  - Poster, "American Expeditionary Forces Distinctive Cloth Insignia,", 1919 (Box-folder 42: 9)
  - Poster, "Bekanntmachung! Folgende Zeitungen sind neben den deutschen im Bereich des Gouvernements Lüttich gestattet…,", undated
  - Poster, "Conventional Signs Used in Trench Maps,", undated
  - Poster, "Eine Kundgebung Hindenburgs an das deutsche Volk,", 1918 September 2
  - Poster, "To the Editor" [War Risk Insurance], 1919 August 4